{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Metal Awning \u0026 Patio Cover Companies","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"__cache./api/resource/task/interview/40452/":{"taskOID":40452,"originalTaskOID":40452,"setID":743,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":500682,"questionDisplayText":"Location of Awning","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Where will the awning(s) or patio cover be installed?","shortQuestionText":"Where will the awning(s) or patio cover be installed?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":7005,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Window(s)","answerDisplayText":"Window(s)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2033,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Door(s)","answerDisplayText":"Door(s)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4807,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Porch","answerDisplayText":"Porch","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4604,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Patio","answerDisplayText":"Patio","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1839,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Deck","answerDisplayText":"Deck","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6733,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Walkway or sidewalk","answerDisplayText":"Walkway or sidewalk","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5721,"questionDisplayText":"Features","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What features do you want included in your awning or patio cover? (Select all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5344,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Retractable or roll-up","answerDisplayText":"Retractable or roll-up","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5674,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Side panels","answerDisplayText":"Side panels","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2892,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Gutters","answerDisplayText":"Gutters","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5770,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Skylights","answerDisplayText":"Skylights","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1289,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Ceiling Fan","answerDisplayText":"Ceiling Fan","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5506,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Screens","answerDisplayText":"Screens","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3603,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Lights","answerDisplayText":"Lights","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":7,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":500682,"questionDisplayText":"Location of Awning","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Where will the awning(s) or patio cover be installed?","shortQuestionText":"Where will the awning(s) or patio cover be installed?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":7005,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Window(s)","answerDisplayText":"Window(s)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2033,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Door(s)","answerDisplayText":"Door(s)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4807,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Porch","answerDisplayText":"Porch","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4604,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Patio","answerDisplayText":"Patio","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1839,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Deck","answerDisplayText":"Deck","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6733,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Walkway or sidewalk","answerDisplayText":"Walkway or sidewalk","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":7005,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Window(s)","answerDisplayText":"Window(s)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2033,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Door(s)","answerDisplayText":"Door(s)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4807,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Porch","answerDisplayText":"Porch","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4604,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Patio","answerDisplayText":"Patio","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1839,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Deck","answerDisplayText":"Deck","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6733,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Walkway or sidewalk","answerDisplayText":"Walkway or sidewalk","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5721,"questionDisplayText":"Features","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What features do you want included in your awning or patio cover? (Select all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5344,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Retractable or roll-up","answerDisplayText":"Retractable or roll-up","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5674,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Side panels","answerDisplayText":"Side panels","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2892,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Gutters","answerDisplayText":"Gutters","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5770,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Skylights","answerDisplayText":"Skylights","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1289,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Ceiling Fan","answerDisplayText":"Ceiling Fan","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5506,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Screens","answerDisplayText":"Screens","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3603,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Lights","answerDisplayText":"Lights","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5344,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Retractable or roll-up","answerDisplayText":"Retractable or roll-up","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5674,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Side panels","answerDisplayText":"Side panels","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2892,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Gutters","answerDisplayText":"Gutters","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5770,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Skylights","answerDisplayText":"Skylights","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1289,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Ceiling Fan","answerDisplayText":"Ceiling Fan","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5506,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Screens","answerDisplayText":"Screens","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3603,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Lights","answerDisplayText":"Lights","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":7,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","__cache./api/resource/task/40452/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":40452,"taskName":"Metal Awning or Patio Cover - Install or Replace","taskDescription":"Install or Replace Metal Awnings or Patio Covers","xmTaskDescriptor":"Metal Awning \u0026 Patio Cover Companies","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":16,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"Metal window retractable covers Patio","textMessagingName":"Inst Metal Awn","rolloverLongDesc":"Awnings provide shade to exterior spaces as well as prevent hot summer sunshine from heating interior spaces \u0026 fading fabrics. Many metal units use a slat design to provide shade in summer \u0026 allow sunlight to penetrate in winter when the angle of the sun is lower. Note separate categories for metal awning repairs, fabric awnings, shutters \u0026 window tinting.","rolloverShortDesc":"Usually aluminum.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Install or Replace Metal Awnings or Patio Covers.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Metal Patio Cover \u0026 Awning Installation \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Replace Metal Patio Cover","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":7,"acceptGoal":3,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":0,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Metal Awning or Patio Cover Install","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Metal Awning or Patio Cover - Install or Replace","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Metal Awning and Patio Cover Project","urlName":"Metal-Awning-or-Patio-Cover-Install-or-Replace","taskConsiderationId":1,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":false,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Metal Patio Cover \u0026 Awning Installers - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | HomeAdvisor","searchKeywords":"metal awning, porch, awning, retractable awning, retractable, porch cover, metal","emcCategoryOid":-12007,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":743,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true}